<xml><txt><metadata><ep><epTitle>Moaning <fam>Lisa</fam></epTitle><szn>01</szn>x<epNum>06</epNum></ep><date>05/19/98</date> <runtime>04:21</runtime></metadata>

<stage>FADE IN</stage>

We open on a sad sh*t of LISA's face.  She is standing on a stool staring into the mirror in her bathroom as a faucet drips nearby.  The door is banged on several times.  <fam>Lisa</fam> sighs.

OUTSIDE, HOMER bangs angrily on the door.

<stage>HOMER</stage><fam>Lisa</fam>!  <fam>Lisa</fam>, are you still in there?  What's the problem?  Did you fall in?  <stage>(chuckles)</stage> <stage>(angrily)</stage> <fam>Lisa</fam>!

<fam>Lisa</fam> finally opens the door and steps out but before <fam>Homer</fam> can enter, BART runs past him.

<stage>BART</stage>Sorry, Dad.  Women and children first.

<stage>HOMER</stage>What the---!?

<fam>Bart</fam> locks the door on him and <fam>Homer</fam> continues banging.  <fam>Lisa</fam> stares at the scene.

FADE TO BLACK

QUICK FADE IN

The kitchen, a bit later.  <fam>Bart</fam> eats cereal while <fam>Marge</fam> washes dishes.  <fam>Homer</fam> suddenly runs in.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Where the hell are my keys?  Who stole my keys?  Come on, I'm late for work!

<stage>MARGE</stage>Oh, <fam>Homer</fam>, you'd lose your head if it weren't securely fastened to your neck.

<stage>BART</stage>Did you check the den?

<stage>HOMER</stage>The den!  Great idea.

<fam>Bart</fam> follows <fam>Homer</fam> as he searches inside a couch.  Various objects like eaten apple cores and pencils fall out.

<stage>BART</stage>Warm.  No, cold.  Colder, ice cold.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Do you know where my keys are?

<stage>BART</stage>No, I'm talking about your breakfast.

<fam>Bart</fam> laughs as <fam>Homer</fam> growls and raises his hands to strike.

<stage>BART</stage>Did you try the rumpus room?

<stage>HOMER</stage>Rumpus room?  Great idea.

As he runs past the front door, he spots <fam>Lisa</fam>.

<stage>LISA</stage>Oh, Dad.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Huh?

She points.  The keys are still in the door lock.

<stage>HOMER</stage>D-oh!

<stage>BART</stage>Oh, <fam>Homer</fam>!

<stage>LISA</stage>Here.

<fam>Marge</fam> suddenly runs in.

<stage>MARGE</stage>I'm sorry, everybody but I've only got two cupcakes for the three of you.

<stage>BART</stage>Well, Mom, one of us has scarfed down more than enough cupcakes over the past three decades to keep a ---

<stage>HOMER</stage><fam>Bart</fam>!

<stage>LISA</stage>Just take mine.  A simple cupcake will bring me no pleasure.

She walks out of the room.  <fam>Homer</fam> and <fam>Bart</fam> are confused for a second, then--

<stage>BART</stage>Ho ho, yeah!

<stage>HOMER</stage>All right.

They high five each other.

FADE TO BLACK

<stage>QUICK FADE IN</stage>

The music class inside school.  MR. LARGO, the teacher, conducts the class.

MR.<stage> LARGO</stage>All right, class.  From the top.  One, and two, and three, and--

The class plays a tune.

MR.<stage> LARGO</stage>My country, 'tis of thee la da da da da dee...

Everybody finishes playing but <fam>Lisa</fam> continues a different tune on her saxophone.  Mr. Largo taps his stand several times with a stick.

MR.<stage> LARGO</stage><fam>Lisa</fam>!  <fam>Lisa</fam> Simpson!

She finally stops.

MR.<stage> LARGO</stage><fam>Lisa</fam>, there's no room for crazy bebop in "My Country 'Tis of Thee."

<stage>LISA</stage>But Mr. Largo, that's what my country's all about.

MR.<stage> LARGO</stage>What?

48 wins and no losses, the undisputed champ of this house, Battling <fam>Bart</fam> Simpson!  Whoopee, whoo!  And in the lavender trunks, with a record of zero wins and 48 defeats--- oh, correction, humiliating defeats --- all of them by knockout...!

<stage>HOMER</stage>Must you do this every time?

<stage>BART</stage><fam>Homer</fam> "The Human Punching Bag" Simpson!

The match begins and <fam>Bart</fam>'s character quickly topples <fam>Homer</fam>'s boxer.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Doh!  Stupid joystick!

<stage>BART</stage>Ho ho.  Three seconds folks, a new record!

<stage>HOMER</stage>Hey, no.  I'm not down.  I'm --- get up, you!  Get off the mat.

<fam>Homer</fam>'s character finally stands up.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Okay, here we go.

<stage>BART</stage>Yo, chump, you back again?

<stage>HOMER</stage>Get outta the way!  How come he's not ducking?

<fam>Bart</fam>'s boxer begins brutally smashing <fam>Homer</fam>'s boxer.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Wait a minute.  I can't get my --- Get out of the way, stupid!

<stage>MARGE</stage><fam>Homer</fam>?

<stage>HOMER</stage>Not now, <fam>Marge</fam>!   Get out of the corner!

<stage>MARGE</stage>But they sent a note from school.

HOMER <stage>(to <fam>Bart</fam>)</stage>: What did you do this time, you little hoodlum?  Oops, get outta the way!

<stage>BART</stage>I didn't do it.  Nobody saw me do it.  There's no way they can prove anything.

<stage>MARGE</stage>No, <fam>Bart</fam>, this note isn't about you.

<stage>BART</stage>It isn't?  There must be some mistake.

<fam>Marge</fam> hands a sheet to <fam>Homer</fam>.

<stage>BART</stage>Hey, you're right.  This note's about <fam>Lisa</fam>.

<stage>HOMER</stage><fam>Lisa</fam>?

At this time, <fam>Bart</fam>'s character finally wins the match.  <fam>Lisa</fam> sighs.

FADE TO BLACK <stage>(COMMERCIAL BREAK)</stage>:

<stage>FADE IN</stage>

<fam>Homer</fam> reads the note.

<stage>HOMER</stage><fam>Lisa</fam> refuses to play dodgeball because she is sad.

He looks at <fam>Lisa</fam>.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Well, she doesn't look sad.  I don't see any tears in her eyes.

<stage>LISA</stage>It's not that kind of sad.  I'm sorry, Dad, but you wouldn't understand.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Oh, sure I would, princess.  I have feelings too.  You know, like "My stomach hurts!" or "I'm going crazy!"  Why don't you climb up on Daddy's knee and tell him about it?

<fam>Lisa</fam> sits on <fam>Homer</fam>'s lap.

<stage>LISA</stage>I'm just wondering what's the point?  Would if make any difference at all if I never existed?  How can we sleep at night when there's so much suffering in the world?

<stage>HOMER</stage>Well --- I --- uh --- Come on, <fam>Lisa</fam>.  Ride the <fam>Homer</fam> horsey!

He tosses it her up and down.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Giddyup!  Whee!

<stage>MARGE</stage>Oh, <fam>Lisa</fam>, honey, why don't we go upstairs and I'll draw you a nice hot bath.  That helps me when I feel sad.

<stage>LISA</stage>Sorry, Dad.  I know you mean well.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Thanks for knowing I mean well.

<stage>BART</stage>Gee, <fam>Homer</fam>, looks like you got yourself a real problem on your hands.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Yeah, right.  Uh, <fam>Bart</fam>, vacuum this floor.

<stage>BART</stage>Hey, man, I didn't do anything wrong!

<stage>HOMER</stage>In times of trouble, you've got to go with what you know.  Now, hop to it, boy!

<fam>Bart</fam> begins vacuuming and mutters under her breath.

<stage>BART</stage>Thinks he some big stupid <fam>Homer</fam>.  Oh, man.  Oh, man.  I'll show him.  He thinks he's so big.

He sucks up a whole deck of cards and then walks to <fam>Lisa</fam>, who has arrived back into the room.

<stage>BART</stage>Enjoy your bath?

<stage>LISA</stage>No, not really.

<stage>BART</stage>Oh, too bad.  Well, I certainly had fun vacuuming.  Maybe now I'll get the pleasure of scrubbing your tub.

<stage>LISA</stage>So typical of <fam>Bart</fam>.  All he thinks about is himself.

<stage>BART</stage>Hey, don't say stuff like that about me to Maggie.  She's on my side, anyway.

<stage>LISA</stage>Is not.

<stage>BART</stage>Is too.

<stage>LISA</stage>Is not.

<stage>BART</stage>Is too.

<stage>LISA</stage>Is not.

<stage>BART</stage>Is too!  Watch, I'll prove it.  Maggie, come to the one you love best.

Maggie hops off the couch.

<stage>LISA</stage>No, Maggie.  Come here, girl.  Come to me.

<fam>Bart</fam> holds out a rattle toy.

<stage>BART</stage>Come on, Maggie!  The choice is obvious.

<stage>LISA</stage>No, Maggie.  Don't go for the glitter.  Look for substance.

Maggie looks from side to side.

<stage>LISA</stage>All right, Maggie, just go to <fam>Bart</fam>.

<stage>BART</stage>Exactly, come to the one you love best.

Maggie crawls forward and hugs the TV.

FADE TO BLACK

<stage>QUICK FADE IN</stage>

<fam>Bart</fam> and <fam>Homer</fam> play the game again.  on the screen, the same two fighters duke it out.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Oh, no!  Come on!  Don't let the --- Ahh, oh no!  Not again! Get over to the righ---ahh!

<fam>Bart</fam> wins once again.

<stage>BART</stage>Gee, Dad, you're really bad at this.

<stage>HOMER</stage>I am not.  It's just that I --- <stage>(saxophone plays in background)</stage> --- couldn't concentrate with that infernal racket.  <fam>Lisa</fam>!  <fam>Lisa</fam>!

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam>Homer</fam> barges into <fam>Lisa</fam>'s room.  She continues playing.

<stage>HOMER</stage><fam>Lisa</fam>, what did I tell you about playing that sax-a-ma-thing in the house?

<stage>LISA</stage>I was just playing the blues, Dad.

Her eyes well up with tears and she begins crying.

<stage>HOMER</stage><fam>Lisa</fam>, I'm sorry.  I didn't mean to yell.  Go ahead.  Play your blues if it'll make you happy.

<stage>LISA</stage>No, that's okay, Dad.  I'll just work on my fingering.  Unless my fingers clacking on the keys is too loud for you.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Let's hear it.

<fam>Lisa</fam> quickly presses down keys and clacks.

<stage>HOMER</stage>You just clack as loud as you want, Lis.

He walks out and closes the door.

<fam>Lisa</fam> clacks for several seconds before she hears a sudden saxophone outside.

<stage>LISA</stage>I've gotta find that sound.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

The backyard, where <fam>Lisa</fam> stealthily carries her saxophone from her window to the treehouse and then down the ladder into the backyard.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

<fam>Lisa</fam> walks across a street.  A full moon fills up the background.  The saxophone continues playing.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

<fam>Lisa</fam> walks past an alleyway.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

<fam>Lisa</fam> is in some alleyway.  There are trash cans and dumpsters around her.  Very  dark.  Not exactly the safest area in the world.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam>Lisa</fam> arrives at her destination.  Looking up, she sees an old man sitting on a bridge playing the sax.  The full moon shines above him.

<stage>LISA</stage>That was beautiful.  What's it called?

<stage>OLD MAN</stage>Oh, it's a little tune that I call the "I Never Had an Italian Suit Blues."

FADE TO BLACK

<stage>QUICK FADE IN</stage>

<fam>Marge</fam> and <fam>Homer</fam> lie in their bed, sleeping.  <fam>Marge</fam> suddenly moans.

We go INSIDE HER DREAM...

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

A kitchen.  <fam>Marge</fam>'s Mom has her hands on young <fam>Marge</fam>'s shoulders.  <fam>Marge</fam> is dressed similarly to <fam>Lisa</fam>, except the blue hair.

2,000 fights and he's still on his original quarter.

<stage>BOXING CHAMPION</stage>Okay, who's next?

<stage>EVERY PERSON IN LINE</stage>Me, me, me, me, me, me!

<fam>Homer</fam> stands above them.

<stage>HOMER</stage>No, me!

<fam>Homer</fam> walks over to the champion.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Listen, can you teach me to fight like you do?

<stage>BOXING CHAMPION</stage>I don't think so.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Oh, come on.

<stage>BOXING CHAMPION</stage>I'll tell you what.  I'll do it if you bark like a dog.

<stage>HOMER</stage>You little--- <stage>(barks)</stage>.

BOXING CHAMPION <stage>(laughing)</stage><stage> </stage>You got yourself a deal, Fido.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

Later in the night; everybody has left the arcade.  Only <fam>Homer</fam> and the champion play and <fam>Homer</fam> is clearly very tired.

<stage>BOXING CHAMPION</stage>Well, looks like you're all out of quarters, old man.

<stage>HOMER</stage>That's okay.  With the tips you've given me, I'm gonna pound the tar out of...a certain little smarty-pants tonight.

Footsteps are suddenly heard and the champion's mom arrives.

<stage>MOM</stage>Howie!  I thought I told you to stop wasting your money in this stupid place!

<stage>BOXING CHAMPION</stage>Sorry, Mom.

MOM <stage>(to <fam>Homer</fam>)</stage>: And you!  A man of your age, you should be ashamed of yourself.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Ehh...excuse me, i think I hear my wife calling.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam>Marge</fam> and <fam>Lisa</fam> drive in their station wagon.  <fam>Marge</fam> looks over sadly at <fam>Lisa</fam>.

<stage>MARGE</stage>Now, <fam>Lisa</fam>, listen to me.  This is important.  I want you to smile today.

<stage>LISA</stage> But I don't feel like smiling.

<stage>MARGE</stage>Well, it doesn't matter how you feel inside, you know.  It's what shows up on the surface that counts.  That's what my mother taught me.  Take all your bad feelings and push them down.  All the way down, past your knees, until you're almost walking on them.  And then you'll fit in, and you'll be invited to parties and boys will like you, and happiness will follow.

<fam>Lisa</fam> smiles.

<stage>MARGE</stage>Oh, come on, you can do better than that.

<fam>Lisa</fam> reveals a larger smile.

<stage>MARGE</stage>Oh, that's my girl.

<stage>LISA</stage>I feel more popular already.

She makes her way out of the car and to the front entrance of the school, where two BOYS spot her.

BOY 1: Hey, nice smile.

<stage>LISA</stage>Thanks.

BOY 2: Hey, what are you talkin' to her for?  She's just gonna say somethin' weird.

<stage>LISA</stage>Not me.

BOY 1: You know, I used to think you were some sort of brainiac but I guess you're okay.

<stage>LISA</stage>Uh-huh.

BOY 2: Hey, why don't you come over to my house after practice?  You could do my homework.

<stage>LISA</stage>Ok.

<stage>MARGE</stage>Hmm!

MR.<stage> LARGO</stage>Five minutes, people, five minutes.  Now, Miss Simpson, I hope we won't have a repeat of yesterday's outburst of unbridled creativity.

<stage>LISA</stage>No, sir.

<fam>Marge</fam> grunts.  She smashes the pedal, does a U-turn, and snatches <fam>Lisa</fam> back into the car.

<stage>LISA</stage>Wow, mom!

MR.<stage> LARGO</stage>Hmm, so that's where she gets it.

<fam>Marge</fam> stops the car when they are further away from the school.

<stage>MARGE</stage><fam>Lisa</fam>, I apologize to you.  I was wrong.  I take it all back.  Always be yourself.  You wanna be sad, honey, be sad.  We'll ride it out with you.  And when you get finished feeling sad, we'll still be there.

<fam>Lisa</fam> inches over to hug <fam>Marge</fam>.

<stage>MARGE</stage>From now on, let me do the smiling for both of us.

<stage>LISA</stage>Ok, Mom.

<stage>MARGE</stage>I said you could stop smiling, <fam>Lisa</fam>.

A big grin is on <fam>Lisa</fam>'s face.

<stage>LISA</stage>I feel like smiling.

They smile at each other.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

The living room, where <fam>Bart</fam> and <fam>Homer</fam> each have a controller in their hands.  <fam>Homer</fam> has a wicked look on his face.

<stage>BART</stage>I'm gonna knock you out one more time, and that's it.  This is getting boring, man.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Just try not to k*ll me too hard, son.  <stage>(chuckles)</stage>.

The two fighters smash at each other.

<stage>BART</stage>Whoa!

<stage>HOMER</stage>Kid, tonight's not your night.

<stage>BART</stage>All right, man, you asked for it.  No more Mr. Nice Guy.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Aha!  Blocked it.  Haha!  You missed me.

They both grunt.

<stage>BART</stage>Oh!

<stage>HOMER</stage>Heh heh heh.  I got you.  Ooh.  Don't try that, I got you blocked.

<fam>Homer</fam>'s character punches <fam>Bart</fam>'s character around the entire ring.

<stage>HOMER</stage>And the crowd is on its feet as Hurricane <fam>Homer</fam> moves in for the k*ll!

<stage>MARGE</stage>Boys, I'd like your attention, please.

<stage>HOMER</stage>Quiet, <fam>Marge</fam>!  This is my moment.  <fam>Bart</fam> "The Bloody Pulp" Simpson is on the ropes.  He is hoping I'll put him out of his misery.  Well, you're in luck, <fam>Bart</fam>.  Here comes my right!

<fam>Homer</fam> is about to b*at <fam>Bart</fam> when---

The TV shuts off.  <fam>Marge</fam> shows the plug to <fam>Homer</fam>.

<stage>HOMER</stage>My game, my game!  I could have b*at the boy!  <fam>Marge</fam>, how could you?  I was so close.<stage>MARGE</stage>I'm sorry, but this is more important than that silly, loud game.<stage>BART</stage>You're right, Mom.  I'd just like to use this occasion to announce my retirement, undefeated from the world of video boxing.

<fam>Homer</fam> sobs.<stage>MARGE</stage>Oh, calm down, <fam>Homer</fam>.  <fam>Lisa</fam> has an idea that she thinks would be fun for the whole family.

<fam>Homer</fam> moans.

FADE TO BLACK

<stage>QUICK FADE IN</stage>

The entire family is at the club.  "Bleeding Gums" Murphy is on stage.

"BLEEDING GUMS"<stage> MURPHY</stage>This next song was written by a friend of mine, one of the great little ladies of jazz.

Murphy lifts up his sunglasses in a motion to <fam>Lisa</fam>.  Murphy and his band begin to play.  The entire Simpson family taps along.

"BLEEDING GUMS"<stage> MURPHY</stage>

I got this bratty brother
He bugs me every day
And this mornin' my own mother
Gave my last cupcake away
My dad acts like he belongs, y'all...
He belongs in the zoo

<stage>HOMER</stage>What?!

"BLEEDING GUMS"<stage> MURPHY</stage>

I'm the saddest kid
In grade number two

Murphy peforms a solo as credits appear.

It continues to play as an outside sh*t of the club is shown.  CREDITS continue until...

FADE OUT

THE END</txt></xml>